Guide to the Paper Tiger Television Archive, ca. 1981-2014 MSS.276
Fales Library and Special Collections
The Paper Tiger Television Archive
1981-2014
Fales Library and Special Collections
Paper Tiger Television Collective (Firm)
MSS.276
143.25 Linear Feet
4 websites in 4 archived websites.
Paper Tiger Television is a non-profit, volunteer-based video collective founded in 1981, which has produced weekly public access television programming that critiques media, culture, and politics. The Paper Tiger Television Archive contains papers, objects, and media that document the running of the organization, the production of the television programming, and all other activities of the collective. Materials in the 2016 Accretion included audio and video recordings and Betamax masters of broadcasts, and CDs.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Paper Tiger Television Archive was donated to NYU's Fales Library by the Paper Tiger Television Collective in 2010. Accretions were donated in 2016 by Julie Ludwig, Paper Tiger Television, and in 2018 by Marisa Holmes. Further accretions were donated in 2019.
http://papertiger.org/, http://blog.papertiger.org/, and http://papertigertv.blogspot.com/ were initially selected by Tamiment curators and captured through the use of The California Digital Library's Web Archiving Service in circa 2007-2009 as part of the Alternative Mass Media / News Web Sites Web Archive. In November 2015, these websites were migrated to Archive-It. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website. In 2015, these seeds were transferred to the Fales Library. In 2018, http://weinterruptthisprogram.org/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2019.057.
Take Down Policy
Archived websites are made accessible for purposes of education and research. NYU Libraries have given attribution to rights holders when possible; however, due to the nature of archival collections, we are not always able to identify this information.
If you hold the rights to materials in our archived websites that are unattributed, please let us know so that we may maintain accurate information about these materials.
If you are a rights holder and are concerned that you have found material on this website for which you have not granted permission (or is not covered by a copyright exception under US copyright laws), you may request the removal of the material from our site by submitting a notice, with the elements described below, to the special.collections@nyu.edu.
Please include the following in your notice: Identification of the material that you believe to be infringing and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; your contact information, such as an address, telephone number, and email address; a statement that you are the owner, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed and that you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and made under penalty of perjury; and your physical or electronic signature. Upon receiving a notice that includes the details listed above, we will remove the allegedly infringing material from public view while we assess the issues identified in your notice.
Arrangement
This collection is divided into 14 series. The folders in each series are arranged alphabetically, with the exception of the financial matierials and the photographs, which are arranged chronologically. The series are:
Series I: Administrative Files
Series II: Activities
Series III: Publicity
Series IV: Financial Material
Series V: Posters and Maps
Series VI: Photographs
Series VII: Video recordings
Series IX: Objects - NO RESEARCHER ACCESS
Series X: Digital Objects
Series XI: 2016 Accretion
Series XII: 2016 August Accretion
Series XIII: 2019 Accretion
Series XIV: Archived Websites
Historical Note
Paper Tiger Television is a New York-based, non-profit, volunteer video collective founded in 1981. The collective has produced weekly public access television programming that critiques media, culture, and politics. Since its creation, Paper Tiger TV has produced more than 320 videos that aim to expose and fight against the corporate control of mainstream media. These programs have been shown nationally on public access television stations, and internationally in screenings and installations.
In 1985, Paper Tiger Television established Deep Dish TV Satellite Network, the first national public access satellite network. Deep Dish TV has since become independent of Paper Tiger TV; however, the two organizations collaborated extensively in 1991 to produce the Gulf Crisis Television Project, a ten-part series exploring many aspects of the Gulf War.
Paper Tiger Television has also been active in social and media activism. Members of the collective have organized several workshops and programs that enable at risk youths and other marginalized groups to have their own voice and become their own advocates. Several of the videos produced through these workshops and programs have gone on to be shown in film festivals and screenings.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact special.collections@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Content
The Paper Tiger Television archive consists of the records and materials created and used during the planning and production of the video collective's programming. The archive contains Paper Tiger TV's administrative and financial records, meeting notes, correspondence, job applications, newspaper clippings, mailing lists, and publicity for the collective. It also contains photographs of the collective and the production of their shows, audiovisual elements, objects such as backdrops, "crankees" (hand-painted scrolls used to display credits in videos), and props. Materials in the 2016 Accretion included audio and video recordings and Betamax masters of broadcasts, and CDs.
Audiocassettes.; Photographs.; Props (object genres); Videocassettes.; Printed ephemera.; Politics and government -- Television programs.; Activists -- United States -- 1980-2011; Public Access Television -- New York.; Minutes (administrative records); Publicizing.; Financial records; Clippings (information artifacts); Paper Tiger Television Collective (Firm); Deep Dish TV Network
- Series I: Administrative Files
  Scope and Content
  This series contains the papers created during the day to day activities and administration of the Paper Tiger TV office. It includes meeting notes, correspondence, job applications, newspaper clippings, mailing lists, and all other office materials.
  - 911 Emergency Employment Clearing House, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Access Orbit Binder, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Access Orbit Survey, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Activist Group contact list, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Activism info - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agenda, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agendaaaa, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alliance for Community Media, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alliance for Community Media - Affiliate Member Recruitment Kit, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "Alternative Communication Strategies in Third World Countries", 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Film Institute - logs, info, etc..., Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Anti-war movement, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Apple Bytes - NYV - ITP [layout of computer icons], 1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Artist Residence - call for applications, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Association of Indepedent Video and Filmmakers (AIVF) event board (1 of 3), 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - AIVF event board (2 of 3), 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - AIVF event board (3 of 3), 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - AIVF - Paper Tiger TV membership benefits, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Austria - "Krieg" exhibit subject file (German), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - B's Study of PTTV - proposal (Berit Nilsen Bua), Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - BFVF Satellite - proposal, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bicycle Tour, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Book proposal, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Brainlink / ISP info, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "Brand Positioning for Nonprofits" guide, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bronxnet (public access files), 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "Budgeting for Grant Proposals" guide, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Case covers (1 of 2), Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Case covers (2 of 2), Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Case Covers and "Freeing the Media" labels, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Cathy Scott's file, Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Cherry Tree Association newsletter, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Clippings - big corporations, Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Clippings - Business Week, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Clippings - CIA, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Clippings - gender and social roles, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Clippings - IMF, Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Clippings - newspapers and the press, Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Collage - Rudy Giuliani, Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - (Collateral Damage) Brown U. Contract, Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Communications issues, Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Contract - consultants, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Contracts / Releases, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Contract - WTO: Free Speech TV, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Copyright - Library of Congress application, Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence - Access Orbit Thank Yous, Random groups we've approved, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence - Alternative publications, Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence - Cathy Scott, Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence - Dan Marcus, Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence - Dee Dee Halleck, Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence - Fan postcards and letters, Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence - Fanmail, Undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence - Gulf Crisis TV Project, Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence - Linda Iannacone, Undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence - Media / Political organizations, Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence - PTTV general, Undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence - PTTV general, Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence - PTTV San Francisco, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Postcards, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - PBS, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Randi Cecchine, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Support letters, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Curriculum Guide - "graphics" folder, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Curriculum Vita - Michael Eisenmenger, c. 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Dee Dee Halleck - Public Broadcasting, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Deep Dish TV - call for tapes - "The Nation Erupts", 1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Deep Dish TV - contact list for Gulf Crisis TV, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Deep Dish TV - directory, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Deep Dish TV - member list, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "The Discreet Art of the Bourgeoisie" - The Nation, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Distribution Agreement, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Distribution Contract - AIMN and ITF, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Distribution possibilities, Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - DIVA TV Press Pass, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Drugs and Medicine subject file, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Duplication services, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Felix Survey, Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Film images - Hollywood, etc..., Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Flyer and newspaper clippings, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Form letters, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Forms - masters, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24A)
  - "Free Radio in Japan" by Tetsuo Kogawa, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Free Speech TV - invoices file, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Free Speech TV - licensing agreement (1 of 2), Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Free Speech TV - licensing agreement (2 of 2), Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Freedom of Information, Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - French and Dutch Video - Cinema Action, Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Fundraiser files etc... - freedom of information request, Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Fundraiser file, etc... - fundraisers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - General Admin. binder, Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Graphics and images, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Gulf Crisis - articles, Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Gulf Crisis TV - call for tapes, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Gulf Crisis TV - carry list, Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Gulf Crisis TV - contact information on index cards, Undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Gulf Crisis TV - original proposal, Undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Hands Off! War Resisters League booklet, Undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Health Insurance research - Tara, Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - "Hey Hobbes, What's a Paper Tiger?" cartoon, Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - History of police brutality in the Latino community - research, Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Holiday party invitations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Independent Media Distribution Alliance, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Intern log book, Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - International media communications - subject file, Undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - IMF - World Bank, Undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - International public access listing, Undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Internship info, Undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Inventory - storage space, Undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Invoices file - Girls Inc., Undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Invoice list, Undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Invoice and phone codes, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Japanese visitors - invoices file, Undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Job announcement, Undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Job announcement, Undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Job Committee, Undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Job descriptions, misc., Undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Job file, Undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Jobs / Resumes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Ken Ives - "Caña Amarga" - in Spanish, Undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - La Voz Popular - notes and materials, Undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Libraries for the Future - Telecom Toolbox, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Licensing agreements, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Lightworks - Access Orbit / Policy stuff, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - List of mentions in publications, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - List of public access stations (300) &(800), Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles stuff filw - Mailing lists, etc..., Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Lower East Side Girls Club - invoices file, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Mailing list additions, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mailing list - address corrections, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Mailing list forms and requests, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Mailing list - fundraiser files, etc..., Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Mailing list - guest book, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Mailing list - Gulf Crisis TV, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Mailing list - LA Outreach, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 12A)
  - Mailing list - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Mailing list / organizational research (1 of 2), 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Mailing list / organizational research (2 of 2), 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Mailing list - press, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Mailing list and signin book for Whitney exhibit, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Mailing list sign up sheet, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Mailing lists / tape lists, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Mailing list - to enter, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Mailing list - VHS distribution, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Malcolm X Grassroots Movement - info sheet, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Materials for the arts, Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Materials for the arts, Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Media Alliance newsletter - Communications arts, Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Media Rights article, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - MediaRights.org information, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Media Theory (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Media Theory (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Meeting agenda, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Meeting agenda, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Meeting notes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Meeting notes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Meeting notes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Meeting notes, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Meeting notes, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Meeting notes - distribution committee agenda, Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Meeting Retreat Notes, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Message Books, 12/1990 - 1/1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Message Book, 1/1991 - 2/1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Message Book, 2/1991 - 3/1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Middle East activist group contact list, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Middle East resources, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous administrative stuff, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - "Mississippi Burning" contract, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Mixed photocopies, clipart, etc..., Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Mobilization for Global Justice literature, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Moscoe, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - National news media contact list, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - NAMAC - resource guides and info, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - New Movement / Security response, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Newsletters - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings - in German, Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Next Agenda, Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - NFLCP members - 11/85, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Notebook - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Notes and fragments, Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - NYCCRM, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - NYSCA distribution questionaire, Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - NYSCA Grant overview sheets, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 22A)
  - Oil company logos, Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Operation class war, Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Operation Storm the Media - Rights to Laurie Anderson song, Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Other public access channels, Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Outreach to public access stations and activist follow-up, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Palestine outreach (and unsuccessful outreach), Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - PTTV collective structure, Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - PTTV CV 1998 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - PTTV diversity training material (1 of 2), Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - PTTV diversity training material (2 of 2), Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - PTTV fact sheet, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - PTTV general descriptions, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - PTTV Handbook, Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - PTTV Party like it's 1999 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - PTTV phone list, Undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - PTTV quotes (handy exerpts), Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - PTTV resume of sorts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - PTTV retreat in Willow, NY, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - PTTV roster phone lists, Undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - PTTV Southwest, Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - PTTV stationary, Undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - PTTV videography / show lists, Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - "Papers" - public television, Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - 'People's Radio' zine, Undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Petty cash forms, Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Phone lists, Undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Photos out, Undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Prayer to TV, Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Preservation - camera shot info, Undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Preservation (correspondence with Tamiment / Wagner library, MARC records, etc...), Undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Preservation (donation cards, notes, plans...), Undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Preservation - dubbing charts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Preservation - glitch glossary and videos, Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Preservation - grant requests, responses, and info, Undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Preservation - IMAP, Undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Preservation - Information on care / preservation, etc., Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Preservation - kit with instructions and logs, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Preservation - Library of Congress public hearing notes, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Preservation - Magnetic media preservation sourcebook, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Preservation - National Film Preservation Foundation, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Preservation notes (Blake's), Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Preservation - Tapes archive info, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Preservation - "Video Preservation: Securing the future of the past", 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Preservation - West Virginia Library Commission Film Services Division, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Press passes - from DIVA TV, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Producer and contact phone numbers, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Prometheus Radio Project, Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Promo materials / resources - Military Myths, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Proposal for a new television network, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Public access station newsletters, Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - "Public Access is Your Right" binder, Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Public access TV subject file, Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Public access TV subject file, Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Public Allies administration, Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Public Allies - job description (Hashim), Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Public Allies organizational info / agreement, Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Puerto Rican rights info, Undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Questionaire responses, Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Quotes about Paper Tiger, Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Racism / discrimination info, Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Radio Show, Undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Recommendation - Hashim, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Release forms, Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Release forms, Undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Releases - Gulf Crisis TV (second series), Undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Releases - Gulf Crisis TV (second series), Undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Request cards to run programs (GCTV), Undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Research aid, Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Resumes, Undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Retreat agendas, Undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Roar! - Printed Matter info, Undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Rock Paper Missiles - Distribution plan, Undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Rwanda information, Undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - San Francisco - various things, Undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Satellite / Public access channel lists, Undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Sign-up sheets, people's info, Undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Sekula, Undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Small publishers co-op / catalog printing, Undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Stickers, Undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Stock letters / forms - for GCTV, Undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Subpoena - for video on Carlisle Action, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 46)